[
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Choose the option that best completes the sentence: The main source of _____ to the government is _____.",
      "options": [
        "A. Production Planning  ",
        "B. Budgeting Revenue",
        "C. Development Taxation",
        "D. Investment Capital"

        
      ],
      "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "This question is from the novel 'The Last Days at Forcados High school'. In chapter two, after the national anthem and assembly prayers, who gave a brief talk welcoming everyone?",
      "options": [
        "A. Seyi Lawal",
        "B. Jimi",
        "C. Mrs Solade",
        "D. The principal"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Choose the option that best fills the gap: Most of his personal ____ stolen.",
      "options": [
        "A. Effects were",
        "B. Affects was",
        "C. Effects was",
        "D. Defects"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "This question is from the novel 'The Last Days at Forcados High school'. What prefect was Jimi?",
      "options": [
        "A. Food prefect",
        "B. Assembly prefect",
        "C. Health prefect",
        "D. The headboy"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "This question is from the novel 'The Last Days at Forcados High school'. Someone called Jimi after he left his food and got outside the gate of his house, Who is it?",
      "options": [
        "A. Jimi uncle",
        "B. Seyi lawal",
        "C. Mr.mallum",
        "D. Ansa"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Choose the option that best fills the gap: The _____ in an attempt to please the workers promised to provide for them an ____ as soon as possible.",
      "options": [
        "A. Commitee/ accommondation",
        "B. Comittee/ acommodation",
        "C. Committe/accommodasion",
        "D. Committee/ accommodation"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that has the same consonant sounds as the one represented by the letters underlined: Straight",
      "options": [
        "A. Struggle",
        "B. Waste",
        "C. Waist",
        "D. Stare"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Choose the option that best fills the gap: It has been confirmed that the election ____ held in July next year.",
      "options": [
        "A. Will be",
        "B. Is being",
        "C. Has been",
        "D. Have being"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "This question is from the novel 'The Last Days at Forcados High school'. What was the early morning surprise Jimi get while he was still half-asleep?",
      "options": [
        "A. Mrs Solade’s return",
        "B. Mr. Solade’s return",
        "C. Tupac Shakur’s return",
        "D. Wole’s return"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that rhymes with the given word: Breeze",
      "options": [
        "A. Stress",
        "B. Chess",
        "C. Free",
        "D. Trees"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Select the wrongly spelt words",
      "options": [
        "A. Quite",
        "B. Beleive",
        "C. Proceed",
        "D. Advise/advice"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "From the options, choose the word(s) that best fill the gap: If the armed robbers ____ caught, they would have been lynched.",
      "options": [
        "A. Would be",
        "B. Have been",
        "C. Are",
        "D. Had been"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "Shakespearian ____ are generally the victims of circumstance.",
      "options": [
        "A. Heros",
        "B. Heroses",
        "C. Hero",
        "D. Heroes"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "The brave officer ____ the time bomb",
      "options": [
        "A. Diffused",
        "B. Druse",
        "C. Defused",
        "D. Difused"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "subject": "English (NABTECH)",
      "question": "This question is from the novel 'The Last Days at Forcados High school'. Who was the best student in chemistry?",
      "options": [
        "A. Ansa",
        "B. Caro",
        "C. Nene",
        "D. Jimi"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "C"
    }
  ]